PUNEET SHIVAKERI

UX DESIGNER

I have seven years of experience creating intuitive and visually appealing digital experiences for users as a UI developer and graphic designer. I am now looking to broaden my skill set and advance my career by taking on a full-time position as a UX designer.

My recent completion of the Google UX Designer Professional Certificate has provided me with a thorough understanding of the user-centered design process as well as the ability to apply industry-standard design principles to solve complex problems. I am passionate about creating aesthetically pleasing and easy-to-use user experiences, and I am excited to apply my skills and expertise to a new challenge.

CONTACT

+91 990 087 9399

puneet.shivakeri@gmail.com

<u>uxps.tech</u>

(Bengaluru

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering | Computer science

2006-2010 | VTU | Kalaburgi, INDIA Appa Institute of Engineering and Technology

Nutan Vidyalaya Pre-University College

2004 - 2006 | Kalaburgi, INDIA Science

Pragnya School

Kalaburgi, INDIA KSEEB- Board, Karnataka

ABILITY

Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability Testing
UX Research
Visual Design
UX Analysis
HTML/HTML5
CSS



View Certificate

EXPERIENCE

UI Developer
 Mindtree Ltd
 April 2021 to October 2021

 UI Developer & Graphic Designer KM Global Techmanage Service Dec 2014 to April 2021

CERTIFICATION

 Google UX Design Professional Coursera

Mar 2023

• ISTQB Certification

Indian Testing Board 2012

SOFTWARE SKILLS











